

Skills

Languages

HTML
CSS
JavaScript
C#
Typescript



Frameworks

Node JS ASP.NET



Utilities

Visual Studio VS Code MS Office Git GitHub



Extras

Unity Engine Blender



Human Languages

Brazilian Portuguese English Spanish Japanese



Contact

- São Paulo SP Brazil
- **1** +55 (11)97760-2862
- uno.braid@gmail.com
- in www.linkedin.com/in/joeisrael
- nttps://github.com/joe-israel
- https://stackoverflow.com/use rs/14956131/joe-israel
- ★ https://joe-israel.github.io/

JOSÉ ISRAEL

WEB AND APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER

About

I am a hardworking and ambitious individual with a great passion for the web and applications industry. I am currently in my first year of studying Computer Systems Analysis at FATEC São Paulo College (Brazil).

I have excellent communication skills, enabling me to effectively communicate with a wide range of people. More than 5 years of self studying, personal projects and online courses about different areas are also accounted for.

I am seeing a full-time position in the industry in which I can put into practice my knowledge and earn a lot of field experience, ultimately benefiting the operations of the organization that I work for.

- ✓ Available to immediate start, remotely or overseas.
- ✓ Brazilian and Italian citizenship.

Experience

2012 - 2013

Freelancer

Web Developer, Brazil Junior web developer that made websites for local business.

2021 - Present

Disbots

Lead Developer, Brazil
I am a team lead that is responsible for the development of Discord bots, using Discord API and Node JS.

Education

2012

Web Design Course

SESC SENAI, Brazil

A 200 hours Web Design course that included up-to-date concepts and workflows.

2014 - 2016

Mechatronics Technologist

Centro Paula Souza, Brazil

A 3 years technologist course integrated with high school.

2021 - Present

Computer Systems Analysis Bachelor

FATEC São Paulo, Brazil

Attending my first year. Apart from coding and developing systems, analyzing and improving existing ones is a very interesting area for me.